17hats.com 2019-05-23

# 17hats

This Privacy Policy describes how 17hats collects and uses the personal information of users of the 17hats service (the "Service") and website.

The privacy of your data is very important to us. We’ll only ever access your account if we need to assist you with a problem or to resolve a software bug.

### The information we collect

We may collect your name, company name, postal address, email address, phone number, password, or other information you directly give us on our Service.

We automatically log information about you and your computer. For example, when visiting our Service, we may log your computer operating system type, browser type, browser language, the website you visited before browsing to our Service, pages you viewed, how long you spent on a page, access times, Internet protocol (IP) address and information about your use of and actions on our Service. This is done to measure and improve the performance of our Service.

We may log information using "cookies." Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Cookies help us make our Service and your visit better. We use cookies to see which parts of our Service people use and like and to count visits to our Service. (And yep, we still find the use of the word "cookies" kind of adorable.)

We may log information using digital images called Web beacons on our Service or in our emails. We use Web beacons to manage cookies, count visits, and to learn what marketing works and what does not. We also use Web Beacons to tell if you open or act on our emails. Again, this is done to measure and improve the performance of our Service. Nothing more.

17hats uses third parties to gather End User's data from financial institutions. By using our service, you grant our third-party provider the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from the relevant financial institution according to terms of our third-party provider's privacy policy.

When you write in to our support team, we use a third party service to hold onto these conversations, along with your email address or phone number for future support correspondence.

### How we use your information

We use your personal information as follows:

  * to operate, maintain, and improve our sites, products, and services.
  * to respond to comments and questions and provide customer service.
  * to send information including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages.
  * to protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity.
  * to provide and deliver products and services customers request.

### Security of your personal and customer information

We take the security of your personal and customer information very seriously, and so we follow industry-standard protocols to protect it.

The database, including anything you store on 17hats, is encrypted using the industry standard AES-256 encryption algorithm.

Your connection to our site is encrypted and authenticated, using:

  * the TLS 1.2 protocol
  * ECDHE_RSA with P-256 (a strong key exchange)
  * a strong AES_128_GCM cipher

### We never share your personal information

Your personal information is yours, and we deeply respect that! We will never sell your data to anyone, ever, period. Aside from the highly-specific and highly-controlled situations in the next two sections below, we will also never share your data with anyone.

### Service partners and third-party sub-processors

In order to provide our Service, we partner with, and share data, with the following services/sub-processors:

  * For Server Hosting and Metrics:
  *     * Amazon Web Services - hosting services
    * Cloudflare - site performance and security
    * Google Analytics - website metrics
    * Datadog - server metrics
  * For Payment Processing
  *     * PayPal
    * Plaid
    * Stripe
    * Square
    * Authorize.net
  * For SMS Notifications
  *     * Twilio
  * For Banking Integration
  *     * Finicity
    * Yodlee
    * Intuit - QuickBooks Online
  * For Customer Support, Site Improvements, and Internal Operations
  *     * Intercom.io - customer support and direct chat
    * Sumo - marketing and site functionality tool
    * Steelhousemedia - marketing tool
    * Facebook Connect and Custom Audience - marketing tool
    * SendGrid - email distribution
    * Customer.io - email distribution
    * Kissmetrics - analytics tool
    * Hotjar - Site visit analysis and UX improvement tool 
    * FullContact - Contact Record Profile Pictures

To be notified in writing when new sub-processors are going to be used with personal data, please email us at [support@17hats.com](mailto:support@17hats.com) and request to be added to the sub-processor notification list.

### Court orders / Law enforcement

If we are required, and only if we are required, to share your information with law enforcement due to a lawful requests such as a subpoena or court order, we must do so, and unless legally prevented from doing so, we will be certain to let you know so that you are informed; outside of a lawful court order, these requests will be outright dismissed.

### Information choices and changes

Most emails we send you will be about your account and our business dealings with you. Sometimes, we may send you non-essential emails, but these emails will have a clear way to "opt-out." If you opt out, you will no longer receive non-essential emails from us.

You can typically remove and reject cookies from our Service with your browser settings. Many browsers are set to accept cookies until you change your settings. If you remove or reject our cookies, it could affect how our Service works for you. So just a heads up on that.

### Deletion of data

If you cancel your account, after 45 days 17hats may, at our sole discretion, delete all of your content; once this content is deleted, it will not be recoverable. Once your active subscription term ends, your content will no longer be accessible, so we advise exporting any reporting, contact lists, or important documents prior to the end of your subscription.

Anything you delete from within your active account will also become immediately inaccessible and cannot be restored. Please very carefully review any warning pop-ups when deleting content/information.

### Contact information

We welcome your comments or questions about this Privacy Policy. You may contact us at any time via Direct Chat from 17hats.com or from within the 17hats application. Simply click on the small green icon in the bottom right corner. You may also email us at [support@17hats.com](mailto:support@17hats.com).

To request access to, changes to, or deletion of your personal information, please do not hesitate to contact our support team.

Questions about our policy/policies - please reach out! We would love to hear from you!

### Changes to this privacy policy

Changes to this policy will be very rare, but from time to time necessary. You can be certain that we will always include the date of publication below for your reference, and that when we make impactful changes, we will make sure to update you.

 _Last Update:  
Wednesday, May 23, 2018_
